[
  {
    "itemName": "ms_enter",
    "roiFront": "1166,148,29,78",
    "roiBack": "1166,148,29,78",
    "description": "进入绘卷主界面"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "ms_scroll_1",
    "roiFront": "170,157,279,192",
    "roiBack": "170,157,279,192",
    "description": "进入卷一"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "ms_scroll_2",
    "roiFront": "490,135,297,210",
    "roiBack": "490,135,297,210",
    "description": "进入卷二"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "ms_scroll_3",
    "roiFront": "836,135,304,210",
    "roiBack": "836,135,304,210",
    "description": "进入卷三"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "ms_scroll_4",
    "roiFront": "137,389,305,206",
    "roiBack": "137,389,305,206",
    "description": "进入卷四"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "ms_scroll_5",
    "roiFront": "491,390,303,207",
    "roiBack": "491,390,303,207",
    "description": "进入卷五"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "ms_scroll_6",
    "roiFront": "835,389,303,204",
    "roiBack": "835,389,303,204",
    "description": "进入卷六"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "ms_back",
    "roiFront": "26,32,49,42",
    "roiBack": "26,32,49,42",
    "description": "退出绘卷主界面"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "ms_close",
    "roiFront": "1142,48,45,36",
    "roiBack": "1142,48,45,36",
    "description": "退出捐献界面"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "ms_contribute",
    "roiFront": "991,572,168,53",
    "roiBack": "991,572,168,53",
    "description": "贡献碎片"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "ms_contributed",
    "roiFront": "108,509,993,190",
    "roiBack": "108,509,993,190",
    "description": "贡献完成跳结算"
  }
]